Once I'm satisfied that I have added
all of the animations I require
it's then a chance to review those
animations and make sure that
everything's working accordingly.
So I have added animations to every
single slide but on this slide, I'm
going to demonstrate how you can change
the way that the animations appear
and the timings of the animations.
So at the moment, when I play the
presentation and I will do that
demonstrate by just playing slide one.
So if I select slide one, and start
the slideshow, nothing happens
until I actually click the mouse
button or press the space bar.
But when I press the space bar,
each of the elements will appear.
But what I want to do is I'd like to
be in a situation where I don't have
to press the space bar so the actual
animations will appear automatically.
So if I go back to the animations tab
and then select the animations pane.
You can see that all of the
animations that are on that slide.
So there are four animations and they all
have a little mouse icon next to them.
So if I just actually hold down
the control key and select all four
of those, rather than doing them
individually, I can then change that
from on click to after previous.
So what that means is that rather
than me having to click, if I view the
slideshow again, just from the slide,
I don't have to click, the information
will start appearing automatically.
As well as that, it may be a case
that I want the actual animations to
not come in as fast so I'd like them
to slow down so they take more time.
Again, what I can do is I
can select all four of the
animations and I can put a delay.
So what I can do there is if I just
added a delay of 1.5 and then preview
that, as you will see the animations
will start to appear a lot more slowly.
And once I'm satisfied that the
timing delay is suitable, I can
then move on to the next slide.
In addition to that, you can actually
change the order of your animations.
So if I wanted the picture on the
right to appear before the picture
on the left, I can highlight the
picture and then move that up.
So if I preview that again now.
The title would come in and then
the picture to the right would come
in before the picture to the left
and then the text at the bottom.
So there are a variety
of things you could do.
So what you can do is you can
have a play around with that and
try changing the automation and
the timings of your animations.